Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Editorial Records 1944-2003 (bulk 1959-1994) MS 3009-RG 6
New-York Historical Society
- Series II.D. Editorial Director Ray Cave Files, 1975-1988; 13 Linear feet in 14 record cartons
  - Subseries II.D.1. Correspondence, 1977-1988; 1.25 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
    While Time Managing Editor, topics include responses to the subjects of articles or sources for the articles; responses to Time readers; use of trademarked names; comments to writers; and responses to external suggestions for covers and articles. Correspondents include editors from other publications, business leaders, and government officials. Items of interest are several letters from the International Center for Photography director Cornell Capa; Henry J. Heinz's response to an article on cholesterol; and correspondence with John Hinckley, Jr. and his parents.
    While at the corporate level as Corporate Editor and Editorial Director, Cave still responds to magazine readers and corresponds with editors from other publications. Correspondence also include invitations to events and to speak; and business social correspondence to Time Inc. staff in the form of congratulations, welcomes, and farewells.
    - 1988 (Offsite-box 1330, Folder 1-4)
    - 1987 (Offsite-box 1330, Folder 5-8)
    - 1987 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R13)
    - 1986 (Offsite-box 1330, Folder 9-10)
    - 1985 (Offsite-box 1330, Folder 11-14)
    - 1984 (Offsite-box 1330, Folder 15-18)
    - 1983 (Offsite-box 1330, Folder 19-20)
    - 1982 (Offsite-box 1330, Folder 21-22)
    - 1981 (Offsite-box 1331, Folder 1)
    - 1980 (Offsite-box 1331, Folder 2)
    - 1979 (Offsite-box 1331, Folder 3)
    - 1978 (Offsite-box 1331, Folder 4)
    - 1977 (Offsite-box 1331, Folder 5)
  - Subseries II.D.2. Court Records, 1980-1985; 2 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
    Court Records contains Ray Cave's copies of court records related to Ariel Sharon's and Synanon Foundation's libel suits against Time Inc. and its magazine Time.
    - Sharon v. Time Inc., 1984 (Offsite-box 2098)
    - Sharon v. Time Inc., 1985 (Offsite-box 2099, Folder 1)
    - Sharon v. Time Inc. [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R17)
    - Syanon v. Time Inc., 1980 (Offsite-box 2099, Item 1-2)
  - Subseries II.D.3. Subject Files: Acting Editorial Director, 1975-1977; 0.5 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    This series contains files that are likely during Cave's tenure as Acting Editorial Director. These records were in a separate grouping from his other subject files. Several of his memoranda refer to him taking action in lieu of Editor-in-Chief Hedley Donovan. Records include his participation in committees, the company-wide hiring and salary freezes, and discussion with Human Resources regarding the union required training program.
    - Books Division, 1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 30)
    - Budget: Books and Arts, 1974 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 31)
    - Contributions Committee, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 32)
    - Cost Control Committee, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 33)
    - FYI, 1974 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 34)
    - Hiring Freeze: General, 1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 35)
    - Hiring Freeze: Books, 1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 36)
    - Hiring Freeze: Fortune, 1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 37)
    - Hiring Freeze: Life, 1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 38)
    - Hiring Freeze: Money, 1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 39)
    - Hiring Freeze: Newsbureau, 1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 40)
    - Hiring Freeze: People, 1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 41)
    - Hiring Freeze: Sports Illustrated, 1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 42)
    - Hiring Freeze: Time, 1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 43)
    - Job Descriptions, 1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 44)
    - Managing Editors' Lunches, 1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 45)
    - Optional Retirement Plan, 1965-1972 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 46)
    - Pioneer Press, 1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 47)
    - Ray Cave Memoranda, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 48)
    - Salary Freeze, 1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 49)
    - Sports Illustrated, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 50)
    - Teleprinter Operators, 1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 51)
    - Time, 1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 52)
    - Time Canada, 1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 53)
    - Trainees, 1975 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 54)
  - Subseries II.D.4. Subject Files, 1974-1989; 9.75 Linear feet in 11 record cartons
    The Subject Files span Ray Cave's tenure as Time Assistant Managing Editor and Managing Editor, Corporate Editor, and Editorial Director. Records include correspondence and memoranda mainly between him and others in the corporate editorial department, Time writing staff, and human resources; comments on and changes to sections of Time; news clippings; studies and reports; and copies of magazine issues. Of interest are his notepads from the 1981 Newstour of Eastern Europe and the Middle East, and the Newsweek folder where he was monitoring Time's rival. His file of "Letters from Notables" includes correspondence from Blanchette Ferry Rockefeller, Dianne Feinstein, and Ansel Adams.
    - Aksyonov, Vassily, 1982 (Offsite-box 1331, Folder 6)
    - American Heritage, 1985 (Offsite-box 1331, Folder 6)
    - American Scene, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 1331, Folder 8)
    - Andropov, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 1331, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report, 1982-1988 (Offsite-box 1331, Folder 10-11)
    - Archives, 1988 (Offsite-box 1331, Folder 12)
    - Archives [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R13)
    - Art directors, 1981-1983 (Offsite-box 1331, Folder 13)
    - Asiaweek: General, 1988 (Offsite-box 1331, Folder 14)
    - Asiaweek: General [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R13)
    - Asiaweek: Chinese Edition, 1987 (Offsite-box 1331, Folder 15)
    - ASME [American Society of Magazine Editors], 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 1331, Folder 16)
    - Association of Independent Colleges, 1979 (Offsite-box 1331, Folder 17)
    - Awards, 1978-1985 (Offsite-box 1331, Folder 18-20)
    - Back of Book, 1977-1985 (Offsite-box 1331, Folder 21-23)
    - Banks, Louis: Report, 1977 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 1)
    - Behavior Section, 1982 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 2)
    - Benefits, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 3-5)
    - Board of Directors, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 6-7)
    - Bonuses, 1980-1988 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 8-13)
    - Bonuses [RESTRICTED], 1981-1988 (Offsite-box R13)
    - Book Excerpts, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 14)
    - Book Excerpts [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R13)
    - Book Projects: Guidelines, 1987 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 15)
    - Brack, Reginald: Meetings, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 16)
    - Budget: General, 1978-1983 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 17)
    - Budget: Magazine Group: Edit, 1986-1989 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 18-21)
    - Budget: Magazine Group: Projections, 1987 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 22)
    - Budget: Monthly Editorial Review, 1988 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 23)
    - Budget Cuts, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 24)
    - Budget Review: Edit Services, 1989 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 25)
    - Budget Review: Fortune, 1989 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 26)
    - Budget Review: Life, 1989 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 27)
    - Budget Review: Money, 1989 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 28)
    - Budget Review: People, 1989 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 29)
    - Budget Review: Sports Illustrated, 1989 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 30)
    - Budget Review: Time, 1989 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 31)
    - Bureaucracy Committee, 1985 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 32)
    - Business Council for International Understanding, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 33)
    - Business Section, 1978-1985 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 34)
    - Bylines, 1977-1981 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 35)
    - Campbell, Ronald [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Offsite-box R13)
    - Car Services, 1987 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 36)
    - Carter, Jimmy, 1978 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 37)
    - Cave Notes from Soviet-American Seminar: March 5, 1980 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 38)
    - CBS Clips, 1987 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 39)
    - Censorship, 1986 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 40)
    - Checkbook Journalism, 1988 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 41)
    - Christmas, 1984-1987 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 42-43)
    - Christmas [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R13)
    - Cliches and Cautions Collection, 1985 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 44)
    - CNN, 1988 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 45)
    - Company Aircraft, 1980-1987 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 46)
    - Compensation Policy, 1980-1986 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 47-48)
    - Compensation Review, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 1332, Folder 49)
    - Company Policy: General, 1977-1988 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 1-3)
    - Company Policy: Securities Transactions [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Offsite-box R13)
    - Comparative Statistics: Magazine Group, 1983-1985 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 4)
    - Conflict of Interest, 1977-1985 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 5)
    - Contract: Carter, Jimmy: Memoirs [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Offsite-box R13)
    - Contract: Heiden, Eric: Photographs [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Offsite-box R13)
    - Contract: Kissinger, Henry: Memoirs, 1978-1982 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 6-8)
    - Contract: Kissinger, Henry: Memoirs [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R13)
    - Contract: Brzezinski, Zbigniew: Memoirs, 1982 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 9)
    - Contract: Donovan, Hedley: Memoirs, 1985 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 10)
    - Contract: Ford, Gerald: Memoirs, 1981 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 11)
    - Contract: Lewis, Carl: Olympic Pictures [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Offsite-box R13)
    - Contract: Liddy, G. Gordon: Memoirs [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Offsite-box R13)
    - Contract: Mondale, Walter: What Is It Like To Run For President, 1984 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 12)
    - Contract: Plimpton, George: 1984 Summer Olympics [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R13)
    - Contract: Reynolds Price: Plains Revisited, 1980 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 13)
    - Contract: Sadat, Anwar: Memoirs [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Offsite-box R13)
    - Contract: Sokolov, Sergei, 1985 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 14)
    - Contract: Shevchenko, Arkady: Excerpts, 1984 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 15)
    - Contract: Solzhenitsyn, A. [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Offsite-box R13)
    - Contract: Weinstein, Alan: Perjury: The Hiss Chambers Case, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 16)
    - Contract: White, Theodore: General, 1982 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 17)
    - Contract: White, Theodore: China, 1983 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 18)
    - Contract: White, Theodore: Elections Story, 1984 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 19)
    - Contract: White, Theodore: In Search of History, 1978 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 20)
    - Contract: White, Theodore: Making of a President, 1984 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 21)
    - Contract: White, Theodore: Making of a President [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R13)
    - Conventions: 1984 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 22-23)
    - Conventions: 1980 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 24-25)
    - Corporate, 1984 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 26)
    - Corporate Manufacturing and Distribution, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 27)
    - Corporate Training Program, 1982 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 28)
    - Correction Policy, 1985 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 29)
    - Council on Liberal Learning, 1985 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 30)
    - Cover Ideas, 1985 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 31)
    - Covers: Late Closing Costs, undated (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 32)
    - Covers: Unrun, undated (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 33)
    - Data Base Publishing, 1983-1985 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 34)
    - Delivery Percentages, 1977 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 35)
    - Edit: Memoranda, 1983 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 36)
    - Election, 1980-1984 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 37-38)
    - Election Issue, 1980 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 40)
    - Employee Opinion Study, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 41-42)
    - Employee Survey Reports, 1985 (Offsite-box 1333, Folder 43)
    - Entertainment and Late Taxi Reports, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 1)
    - Entertainment Weekly, 1988 (Offsite-box 2593, Folder 6)
    - Equipment, 1978-1988 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 2)
      Includes upholstery samples for Cave's office furniture.
    - Expense Account Policy, 1984 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 3)
    - Expenses: Edit Direct, 1983 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 4)
    - Five Year Plan: 1985-1989 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 5)
    - Five Year Plan: 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 6-7)
    - Five Year Plan: Summaries and Cave Memoranda, 1979-1982 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 8)
    - Foreign Corrupt Practices Act, 1979 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 9)
    - Foreign Corrupt Practices Act [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R13)
    - Future of Magazines Report, 1975 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 10)
    - Gardner, Martin: Monthly Report, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 11-12)
      Gardner reports on reviews of budgets and finances on the edit and news services.
    - Gart, Murray, undated (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 13)
    - Guild Contract, 1983 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 14)
    - Haines, R.G.: Time Story, 1984 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 15)
    - Haines, R.G.: Time Story [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R13)
    - Hansel and Gretel, 1984 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 16)
      Materials on Joachim and Renate Franke and the Ministerium für Staatssicherheit, known as the Stasi.
    - Headcount: Edit, 1985 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 17)
    - Heiskell, Andrew, 1980 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 18)
    - Hiring History, 1979-1984 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 19)
    - Hiring History [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R13)
    - Hitler/Hess, 1983 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 20)
      Regarding the Adolf Hitler diaries hoax.
    - Hoffman Case, 1983-1985 (Offsite-box 2593, Folder 7-8)
    - Holidays, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 2593, Folder 9)
    - Home Office Magazine, 1985 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 21)
    - Hostages, 1979 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 22)
    - Howell, Barbara, 1987 (Offsite-box 2593, Folder 10)
    - Human Resources, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 2593, Folder 11)
    - Information Resources Group, 1986 (Offsite-box 2593, Folder 12)
    - Interesting Layouts, 1986 (Offsite-box 2593, Folder 13)
    - Internal Audit Group, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 2593, Folder 14)
    - International, 1985 (Offsite-box 2593, Folder 15)
    - Interview: Brezhnev Issue, 1979 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 23)
    - Interview: Gorbachev Issue, 1985 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 24)
    - Interview: Teng Hsaio-p'ing Issue, 1979 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 25)
    - Investment Week Development, 1984 (Offsite-box 2593, Folder 16)
    - "It's About Time", 1976 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 26)
    - Jaroff, Leon, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 2593, Folder 17)
    - Keith, Larry [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Offsite-box R23)
    - Kennedy, Ray, 1988 (Offsite-box 2593, Folder 18)
    - Kissinger, Henry, 1982 (Offsite-box 2593, Folder 19)
    - Kissinger, Henry, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 27)
    - Kissinger, Henry [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980 (Offsite-box R23)
    - Klingensmith, Mike, 1987 (Offsite-box 2593, Folder 20)
    - Kravitz, Ben-Tzion, 1985 (Offsite-box 2593, Folder 21-22)
    - Late Closing Costs, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 2593, Folder 23)
    - Leaves of Absence, 1980 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 28)
    - Leaves / Sabbaticals, 1987 (Offsite-box 2593, Folder 24)
    - Legal, 1978-1985 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 29-30)
    - Legal, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 2593, Folder 25)
    - Legal, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 2594, Folder 1-3)
    - Legal [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R13)
    - Letters Department, 1980-1985 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 31)
    - Letters Department, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 2594, Folder 4-5)
    - Letters Department [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R13)
    - Letters from Notables, 1977-1985 (Offsite-box 1334, Folder 32)
    - Levine, Mark [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Offsite-box R23)
    - Libel Law Considerations, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 2594, Folder 6)
    - Life: Miscellaneous, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 2594, Folder 7-10)
    - Life: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R23)
    - Life: Century Project, 1988 (Offsite-box 2594, Folder 11)
    - Life: Exhibitions, 1987 (Offsite-box 2594, Folder 12)
    - Life: Ideas, 1987 (Offsite-box 2594, Folder 13)
    - Life: Story Lists, circa 1988 (Offsite-box 2594, Folder 14)
    - Life-TV: Durniak/Giacalone Proposal, 1988 (Offsite-box 2594, Folder 15)
    - LTIP [Long-term incentive plan], 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 1)
    - Lunch Notes, 1981 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 2)
      Includes notes from lunches with Yitzhak Shamir and Shirley Williams.
    - Luncheons with Outsiders, 1981-1985 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 3)
      Includes notes from lunches with IBM, Polaroid, and RCA executives, Secretary of the Navy John Lehman, and Robert Leiken.
    - Lunchtime Forums, 1987 (Offsite-box 2594, Folder 16)
    - Lyford Cay Meetings, 1988 (Offsite-box 2594, Folder 17)
    - Magazine Committee, 1981 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 4)
    - Man of the Year, 1977-1985 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 5-14)
    - Management Training for Editors, 1984 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 15)
    - Managing Editor Appointment, 1977 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 16)
    - Marketing Interview of Cave, 1979 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 17)
    - Matthews, T.S., 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 18)
    - Mauldin, Bill, 1977-1979 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 19)
    - Mauldin, Bill [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R13)
    - McKinsey & Co. Project, 1983 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 20)
    - Media on Time Inc., 1979-1985 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 21-22)
      1 audiocassette (micro-cassette): analog, 1/8 in. tape. On envelope container: "6/28/82. Call from Charles Wallace, LA Times re ABC/Synanon suit settlement."
    - Middle East Conference, 1979 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 23)
    - Munro, Richard J., 1981 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 24)
    - Nation Section, 1978-1984 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 25)
    - New Magazines, 1985 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 26)
    - New Sections, 1981-1985 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 27)
    - News Service: General, 1977-1985 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 28)
    - News Service: Assessment, 1985 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 29)
    - News Service: Assignments and Changes, 1980-1985 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 30)
    - News Service: Budget [empty], undated (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 31)
    - News Service: Headcount, 1984 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 32)
    - News Service: Reorganization, 1985 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 33)
    - News Service: Study, 1985 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 34)
    - Newsstand: Sales, 1975-1986 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 35-45)
    - Newsstand: Time/Newsweek Final Sales Comparison, 1981-1985 (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 46)
    - Newstour: 1985: Far East (Offsite-box 1335, Folder 47-48)
    - Newstour: 1983: Mexico and Central America (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 1)
    - Newstour: 1981: Eastern Europe and Persian Gulf (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 2-3)
    - Newstour: 1978: Africa and Middle East (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 4)
    - Newsweek, 1979-1985 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 5-6)
      Includes audiovisual material.
      1 audiocassette (Microcassette): analog; 2 x 1 5/8 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "Pete." On envelope container: "Tape of phone conversation with Dan Machalaba, WSJ, re Newsweek 2/3/83, 11 A.M."
    - Neiman Fellows, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 7)
    - Notes from the Managing Editor, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 8)
    - Offset, 1981 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 9)
    - Olympics: Summer 1984 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 10-11)
    - Olympics: Winter 1984 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 12)
    - Olympics Coverage, 1980 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 13)
    - Overtime: Art Department, 1985 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 14)
    - Overtime: Picture Department, 1985 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 15)
    - Overtime: Reports, 1985 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 16a)
    - Overtime: Research Staff, 1985 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 16b)
    - Overtime Study, 1983-1985 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 16c)
    - Overtime: Support Staff, 1985 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 17a)
    - Parties, 1980-1985 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 17b-18)
    - Personality Stories, 1981 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 19)
    - Photographers: Rights, 1975 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 20a)
    - Photographers: Rights [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R13)
    - Photographers: Time Inc. Contracts [RESTRICTED], 1973-1975 (Offsite-box R13)
    - Picture Collection, 1977-1982 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 20b)
    - Picture Department, undated (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 21)
    - Picture Policy, 1978-1981 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 22)
    - Picture Week, 1985 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 23)
    - Pope Interview, 1980 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 24)
    - Porambo, Ron, 1980-1986 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 25)
    - Printing Layout?, 1980 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 26)
    - Questions for the 80s Project, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 27)
    - Reader's Digest [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Offsite-box R13)
    - Salaries, 1978-1983 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 28)
    - Scientologists, 1983 (Offsite-box 1336, Folder 29-30)
    - Scientologists [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R13)
    - Seminars, 1978-1985 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 1-2)
    - Senior Editor Candidates, 1984 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 3)
    - Senior Editors, 1979-1985 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 4)
    - Soviet Trip Notes: March 29-April 5, 1980 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 5)
    - Soviets and Cubans in Africa: Talbott Report, 1978 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 6)
    - Special Issue: 60th Anniversary, 1983 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 7)
    - Special Issue: American Renewal, 1981 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 8)
    - Special Issue: Immigrants, 1985 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 9-10)
    - Special Issue: Japan, 1983 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 11)
    - Special Issue: Japan [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R13)
    - Special Issue: Leadership, 1974 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 12)
    - Special Issue: U.S.S.R, 1980 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 13)
    - Spinney Cover Fallout, 1983 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 14)
    - Temporary Help Costs, 1985 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 15)
    - Time: Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 2594, Folder 18-20)
    - Time: Miscellaneous, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 2679, Folder 1-3)
    - Time Australia: General, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 2679, Folder 5-10)
    - Time Australia: Assessment, 1987? (Offsite-box 2679, Folder 11)
    - Time Australia: Board of Directors, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 2679, Folder 12)
    - Time Australia: Board Meetings, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 2679, Folder 13-14)
    - Time Australia: Fairfax Joint Venture Dissolution Term [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Offsite-box R23)
    - Time Education Program, 1986? (Offsite-box 2679, Folder 15)
    - Time/Newsweek: Cover and Color Comparison, 1975-1980 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 17)
    - Time/Newsweek: Edit Pages Report, 1980-1985 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 18-19)
    - Time: Profit History, 1985 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 16)
    - Time: Special Issue: Constitution Bicentennial, 1987 (Offsite-box 2679, Folder 4)
    - Time Writer/Editor History, 1974-1984 (Offsite-box 1337, Folder 20)
    - Time Inc. History: Atheneum, 1979-1985 (Offsite-box 2679, Folder 16)
    - Time Inc. History: Atheneum [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R23)
    - Time Inc. Magazine Group Company, 1988 (Offsite-box 2679, Folder 17)
      Includes information on the rebranding as the group changes from a division to a subsidiary.
    - Time Inc. Year End Summary, 1987? (Offsite-box 2679, Folder 18)
    - Time-Life Alumni Society Directory, 1987 (Offsite-box 2679, Folder 19)
    - Time-Life Books, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 2680, Folder 1)
    - Time-Life Fellowships, 1988 (Offsite-box 2680, Folder 2)
    - Time to Write Project, 1986 (Offsite-box 2680, Folder 3)
    - Travel and Entertainment Costs for all Editorial, 1986 (Offsite-box 2680, Folder 4)
    - Travel and Entertainment Policy, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 2680, Folder 5-7)
    - Trippett, Frank [empty], undated (Offsite-box 2680, Folder 8)
    - Turnover: Magazine Group, 1986 (Offsite-box 2680, Folder 9)
    - TV: Magazines, 1984 (Offsite-box 2680, Folder 10)